A Guide to the Equal Suffrage League of Virginia records, 1908-1938
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Equal Suffrage League of Virginia., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 5-15)
  - Local Chapters., 4 boxes (Box 12-15)
    - Roanoke--Roanoke Equal Suffrage League, 1912-1917, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Roanoke--Roanoke Equal Franchise League, 1915-1916 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Roanoke County, 1916-1917, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Roanoke County--Salem (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Rockbridge County--Goshen (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Rockbridge County--Lexington (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Rockingham County--Harrisonburg (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Shenandoah County--Strasburg (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Shenandoah County--Woodstock (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Smyth County--Marion (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Southampton County (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Staunton, 1914-1916. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Suffolk (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Surry County (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Surry County--Claremont (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Sussex County--Waverly (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Tazewell County (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Tazewell County--Graham (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Warren County--Front Royal (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Washington County (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Williamsburg, 1914-1920, 1936 (see also James City County) (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Winchester (including Frederick County), 1918-1920, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Wise County--Big Stone Gap (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Wise County--Norton (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Wythe County--Wytheville (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - York County (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - 2nd Congressional District, 1917-1919 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - 9th Congressional District (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Series III: National American Woman Suffrage Association records, 1910-1920., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 16-19)
  National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA) contains NAWSA convention programs and proceedings, 1910-1921; constitutions; yearbook; reports; proclamations; recommendations; press releases; history; notes; bulletin; essays; study guides; travel kits; suffrage schools; publications, pamphlets, leaflets, and broadsides; subscription offer; fundraiser; Jeannette Rankin; Susan B. Anthony; and invitations. Also includes materials from NAWSA state and local chapters, other than Virginia.
  - Convention program, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Convention program, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Convention program, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Convention program and ballot, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Convention program and call, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Convention program, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Convention program, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Convention call, schedule, and ballot, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Convention program, 1920 (also Congress of the League of Women Voters) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Victory convention, February 1920 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Convention program, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Convention proceedings, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Convention proceedings, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Convention proceedings, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Convention proceedings, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Convention proceedings, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Convention proceedings, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Convention proceedings and handbook, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions, 1913, 1919, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Yearbook, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer's report, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Report of committee on petition to Congress, ca. 1909 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Woman's Thanksgiving Proclamation, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations, ca. 1920 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Candidates for NAWSA organizion offices (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, 1914-1919 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, February-September 1920 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, [1920] (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Materials on The History of Woman Suffrage (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Suffrage Agriculture--Home and Garden notes I--Suggestions for Work to Increase the Food Supply (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin, number 22, 14 August 1918 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Essays (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Study guide, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Woman's Journal and Suffrage News Traveling Kampaign Kit--suffrage literature (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Woman's Journal and Suffrage News Traveling Kampaign Kit--collected answers to antis (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - National Suffrage Schools--Virginia, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - National Suffrage Schools--Maine (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - A School of Political Education for Women, 19-26 February 1920 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - League of Women Voters Bulletin of the Committee on Food Supply and Demand, February 1920 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - The Declaration of Independence, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - The [Stanley] Bowdle Speech, 12 January 1915 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - A Petition for Woman Suffrage by Federal Constitutional Amendment One Thousand Signers, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Catalogs--publications, plays, etc. (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Sample book of pamphlets and leaflets (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlets--What Women Might Do With the Ballot series (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets--Eminent Opinions on Suffrage (three distinct editions) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Pamphlets--Alice Stone Blackwell (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets--Carrie Chapman Catt (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Pamphlets--Ida Husted Harper (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets--Woman Suffrage in England--Annie G. Porritt (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Pamphlets--Authors B-F (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets--Authors H-M (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlets--Authors N-Y (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlets--no author listed (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Leaflets--Directions to Officers of the Local Clubs, Constitution for the Local Associations, and Political District Organization (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Leaflets--What to Read on Suffrage, March, May 1912 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Leaflets--Alice Stone Blackwell (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Leaflets--Authors A-H (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Leaflets--Authors K-Z (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Leaflets--no author (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Leaflets, mounted--Authors A-Blackwell (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Leaflets, mounted--Authors Blake-D (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Leaflets, mounted--Authors F-N (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Leaflets, mounted--Authors O-U (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Leaflets, mounted--no authors (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Broadsides (folder 1 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Broadsides (folder 2 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Broadsides (folder 3 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Broadsides, foreign language (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Woman's Journal issues and subscription offers, 1909-1910, 1912, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Magazine fundraiser form (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Jeannette Rankin (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Celebration of Susan B. Anthony's 86th birthday, 15 February 1906 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 11 December [1917?], 5 December [1919?] (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Alabama Equal Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Boston Equal Suffrage Association for Good Government (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Business Women's Equal Suffrage League (St. Louis, Missouri) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - College Equal Suffrage League (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Collegiate Equal Suffrage League of New York State calendars, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Wman Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Equal Franchise Society of Pennsylvania (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Equal Suffrage League of Baltimore (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Illinois Equal Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Kentucky Equal Rights Association--National Congressional Campaign Conference of Kentucky, 27-28 March 1916 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Maryland State Equal Suffrage League (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Political Equality Union (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - New England Woman Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina Equal Suffrage League (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Equal Franchise Association (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - South Dakota [Equal Suffrage Association?] (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - West Virginia Equal Suffrage Association (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Woman Suffrage Association of the State of Maryland (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - [Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association?] calendar, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Series IV: League of Women Voters of Virginia, 1920-1938., Extent: 1 box. (Box 20)
  Virginia League of Women Voters records contain constitutions and bylaws; financial statements and pledges; resolutions; state conferences and conventions; Know Your League papers, bulletins; press releases; speeches of Jessie Townsend and others; state elections; education programs; leaflets and broadsides; enrollement forms and other papers. There are also papers and records for the Norfolk and Richmond chapters of the League.
  - Constitution, by-laws, 1920, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - By-laws, 1927-1933 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Financial statement, 1920-1922 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pledges/fees, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Resolution--Kate Waller Barrett, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - State conference, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Convention programs, 1926, 1930, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Know Your League, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins, 1920-1921, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Press releases, 1920, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Jessie Townsend speeches (see also Box 4, Folders 21-23; Box 13, Folders 16-18; Box 20, Folder 25) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Speech of Colonel C. P. Shaw Before the League, 3 October 1921 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - State elections, 1921-1923, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Citizenry and citizenship schools, 1920-1933 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Two Day and Three Day Institutes--tentative programs (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Leaflets (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Broadsides and posters, 1920, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Membership enrollment forms (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Stationery (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--minutes and related papers, 1928-1929 (papers are in original order) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--meeting programs, 1920, 1928-1930 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--membership lists (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--financial records, 1920, 1923, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--Jessie Townsend speeches (see also Box 4, Folders 21-23; Box 13, Folders 16-18; Box 20, Folder 11) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--policewomen (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Norfolk League of Women Voters--miscellaneous papers (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--board meeting minutes, 10 March 1921 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--committee on cook book minutes, 12 February 1921 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Richmond League of Women VotersTreasurer's report, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--officers ballot, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--membership list, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--News Bulletin, May 1927 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--city elections, 1921, 1922, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--application for registration to vote (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--programs, pamphlets, postors, invitations, 1932-1937 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--miscellaneous papers (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Richmond League of Women Voters--stationery (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - 2nd Congressional District League of Women Voters--papers (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Virginia League of Women Voters--conference of district directors, 7 January 1921 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Series V: National League of Women Voters., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 20-22)
  National League of Women Voters records contain organization plans; ballots; by-laws; convention and conference programs; reports and recommendations; bulletins, newsletters, and press releases; and other publications. Also includes publications and papers from states and localities (other than Virginia).
  - Organization plan, ca. 1920 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - By-laws (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Official ballot, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Fourth annual convention, 9-14 April 1923 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Fourth annual convention--speech of Florence E. Allen, 11 April 1923 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Fifth annual convention--local president's dinner, 24 April 1924 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Sixth annual convention, [April?] 1925 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Seventh annual convention, 14-21 April 1926 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Tenth national convention, 22-30 April 1932 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Child welfare conference, [February 1920?] (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Third region--regional conference, 8-9 February 1921 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Ninth conference on the cause and cure of war, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Committee on American citizenship recommendations, [1920?] (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Child welfare committee (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Report covering delinquents, minors, and defectives (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Committee on food supply and demand recommendation, 16 February 1920 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Committee on unification of laws concerning the legal status of women, [1920?] (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Women in industry department report, 14 February 1920 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - League News, February 1931, April 1935 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Third region newsletter, 11 January 1932 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Press releases, 1920, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Achievements of the Years, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Voter Service radio program brochures, January-March 1932 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Lists of publications, 1929, 1935-1937 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Programs of Work, 1919, 1928-1934, 1936-1938 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Program of Work--Department of Government and Child Welfare, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Program of Work--Department of Government and Economic Welfare, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Program of Work--Department of Government and International Cooperation, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Program of Work--Department of Government and Its Operation, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Program of Work--Department of Government and the Legal Status of Women, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Know Your League, 1930, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Department of Efficiency in Government--Budget Making and Administration: With Special Reference to Cities, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Department of Efficiency in Government--Constructive Economy in Local Government, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Department of Efficiency in Government--Know Your County, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Child Welfare--The Background of Our Child Labor Problem, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Child Welfare--Community Care for the Health of the Mother and Young Child, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Department of Child Welfare--Children in Industry, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Department of Government and Child Welfare--Mothers' Aid, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Department of Government and Child Welfare--School Attendance Laws in the United States, April 1935 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Department of Government and Economic Welfare--Buyers Beware, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Department of Government and Economic Welfare--Government and the Consumer, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Department of Government and Education--Large City School Systems, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Department of Government and Education--The Public Library as a Government Service, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Department of Government and Education--School Attendance Laws in the United States, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Special Committee on Immigration Problems--New Immigration and Naturalization Legislation, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Special Committee on Immigration Problems--Immigration and Naturalization Legislation 1924-1932, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Department of Government and International Cooperation--The Conduct of the Foreign Policy of the United States, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Department of Government and International Cooperation--Control of the Munitions Traffic, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Department of Government and International Cooperation to Prevent War--The Root Formula and the World Court, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Department of Government and Its Operation--Trained Personnel for Public Service, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Committee on the Legal Status of Women--Against Equal Rights by Constitutional Amendment: A Reply, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Committee on the Legal Status of Women--Toward Equal Rights for Men and Women, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Committee on the Legal Status of Women--Women's Liability for Jury Service, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Department on the Legal Status of Women--The Nationality of Children, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Department of Government and the Legal Status of Women--The Married Woman and Her Job, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Women in Industry--A Federal-State Employment Service, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Department of Women in Industry--Industrial Standards for Women Workers, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Personnel Campaign Committee--A Handbook for the Personnel Campaign, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - American Neutrality, ca. 1935 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Organization for Public Welfare, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Electing the President, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The ABC's of Unemployment Compensation, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Equal Rights or Human Rights?, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Needed: A New Food and Drug Law, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets on League history, organization, and operation (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Flyer on the bicentennial of George Washington's birth, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - California--The Bulletin of the California League of Women Voters, January, March 1935 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut--The Woman Voter's Bulletin, July-August 1929 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Illinois--The Illinois Voter, March 1929, February, March 1935 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Illinois--Cook County--The Cook County Citizen, February 1935 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Louisiana--Louisiana League of Women Voters' Platform, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts--Bulletin, February-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Minnesota--The Minnesota Woman Voter, July 1929, December 1934-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Missouri--The Missouri League News, July 1929 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Missouri--St. Louis--The League Bulletin, 9 May, 21 June 1931; January-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - New Hampshire--The New Hampshire Woman Voter, January-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - New York--Weekly News, January-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - New York--Education Section--The Next War, by Will Irwin (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - New York--The Bronx--A Money Making Plan, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Ohio--The Ohio Woman Voter, June 1930 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Pennsylvania--The Bulletin of the Pennsylvania League of Women Voters, August 1929 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Rhode Island--News Letter, January 1935 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Wisconsin--The Bulletin of the Wisconsin League of Women Voters, January-April 1935 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Series VI: General and Miscellaneous Files., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 22-28)
  General and Miscellaneous Files contain records, papers, and publications of local, state, and national organizations other than the Equal Suffrage League or the League of Women Voters; papers, documents, and publications by local, state, and federal governments; pamphlets, and leaflets, brochures, and broadsides from England and Ireland. Also contains a variety of miscellaneous items including postcards.
  - Organizations., 3 boxes (Box 22-24)
    - Pro-suffrage resolutions from various organizations, 1918-1919 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Atlanta suffrage organizations--Georgia Harvest Festival--Better Babies Contest, 15-20 November 1915 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Brookland District Citizens' Association (Henrico County, Virginia) papers, ca. 1932 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Cambridge Anti-Suffrage Association (Massachusetts)--Anti-Suffrage Notes numbers 138-139, 23 January 1917 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Conference on Governmental Efficiency (Virginia), 21-22 November 1921 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage, 1915, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Co-operative Education Association leaflet--Home Reading Course (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Co-ordinate College for Women (affiliated with the University of Virginia), 1914 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Democratic Woman's Club souvenier menu, 29 January 1925 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Daughters of the King Constitution and Prayers, Handbook of the Daughters of the King, and envelope, 1913, 1916, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America (Virginia chapter) resolution, December 1919 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Federation of Labor--The Union News Convention Edition, official yearbook, 2 April 1923 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Women's Clubs of Virginia resolution, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Virginia 4-H Club Letter, February 1934, January-February 1934 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Ladies' Athenaeum Club (England) rules, by-laws, list of members, 1910 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - League to Enforce Peace--What the War Meant to Women by Dr. Anna Howard Shaw (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lila Meade Valentine Memorial, 1926-1936 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Men's Equal Suffrage League of Virginia letters, 1911-1912 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Men's League for Woman Suffrage (Virginia) membership lists (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Men's League for Woman Suffrage pamphlets, 1911, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Monroe Centennial Memorial Commission, 4 July 1931 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - National Advisory Council on Radio in Education--Listen and Learn About your Government: Constructive Economy in Government, 20 June-26 September 1933 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - National Child Labor Committee--The Child Labor Bulletin, June 1912 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - National Child Labor Committee pamphlet and leaflets, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - National Committee to Secure Rank for Nurses bulletins, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - National Consumers' League pamphlets, 1912, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - National Consumers' League papers, January 1933, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - [New York City] Consumers' League leaflet, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs--Old Dominion convention, Traveling Through Historyland, 6--11 July 1931 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees press releases, 20-21 August 1920 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - National Kindergarten Association leaflet (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - National Motion Picture League leaflet (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - National Municipal League leaflets, 1911, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - National Woman's Party Campaign Texbook, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - National Woman's Party (Norfolk branch) report, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - National Women's Trade Union League of America pamphlets, 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - National Women's Trade Union League press release, 3 December 1919 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Non-Partisan Senatorial Committee (New York) papers, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - New York State Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage--Woman's Relation to Government,, Mrs. William Forse Scott, 1904 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Odeon Program, 28 March 1919 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Progressive Party pamphlets, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 31)